/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data4_2', {
    title: '4.2 Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
    path: '4.2-order-of-operations-with-whole-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 7 * 2 + 4}',
                answer: '\\input{18}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 7 * 2 + 4}',
                answer: '\\ordops{7 * 2 + 4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve (15 - 10) / 5}',
                answer: '\\input{1}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve (15 - 10) / 5}',
                answer: '\\ordops{(15 - 10) / 5}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 4 / 2 + 9}',
                answer: '\\input{11}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 4 / 2 + 9}',
                answer: '\\ordops{4 / 2 + 9}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 6 - (6 / 3)}',
                answer: '\\input{4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 6 - (6 / 3)}',
                answer: '\\ordops{6 - (6 / 3)}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 7 + 15 / 3}',
                answer: '\\input{12}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 7 + 15 / 3}',
                answer: '\\ordops{7 + 15 / 3}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 3 / (3 * 3 / 3)}',
                answer: '\\input{1}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 3 / (3 * 3 / 3)}',
                answer: '\\ordops{3 / (3 * 3 / 3)}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 15 - ((7 - 4) * 2)}',
                answer: '\\input{9}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 15 - ((7 - 4) * 2)}',
                answer: '\\ordops{15 - ((7 - 4) * 2)}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 15 - 8 * 2 / 4}',
                answer: '\\input{11}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 15 - 8 * 2 / 4}',
                answer: '\\ordops{15 - 8 * 2 / 4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve (28 + 15 / 5) - (22 - 8)}',
                answer: '\\input{17}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve (28 + 15 / 5) - (22 - 8)}',
                answer: '\\ordops{(28 + 15 / 5) - (22 - 8)}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Order Of Operations With Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 27 / 9 + 6 * 8 - (10 + 25)}',
                answer: '\\input{16}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Solve 27 / 9 + 6 * 8 - (10 + 25)}',
                answer: '\\ordops{27 / 9 + 6 * 8 - (10 + 25)}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
